<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Farzad Hayatbakhsh</title>
    <link>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Farzad Hayatbakhsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Monster Fighter</title>
      <link>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/monster-fighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/monster-fighter/</guid>
      <description>A turn-based player-vs-computer game made for Windows. The goal is to fight the enemy monster teams while upgrading yours. You have a limited number of days and must aim to achieve the best score by picking your fights carefully. This game was made in 2022 as a university course project between Farzad Hayatbakhsh and Daniel Cha. This game was made using Java and the Swing GUI Toolkit.
Download Source Code + Java Executable</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pen Website</title>
      <link>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/pen-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/pen-website/</guid>
      <description>A website about pens made in 2020. The purpose is to inform the user about different pens, features, and popular brands of pens. The user is able to modify the website by adding new brands to the database. This was a solo school project made for the year 13 programming class. This website was made using Python, Flask, SQLite, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript.
GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakout</title>
      <link>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/breakout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/breakout/</guid>
      <description>Demo Video
A third-person adventure game made for Android.
The goal is to rescue the hostages and lead them to the exit.
This game was made in 2019 as a school project between Toby Tinker and myself.
My role was programming and level design.
Toby&amp;rsquo;s role was modelling and textures.
This game was made using Unity3D, C#, and Magicavoxel.
Download for Android</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Droid Invasion</title>
      <link>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/droid-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://farzadhayat.gitlab.io/posts/droid-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Demo Video
A first-person shooter game made for Windows. The goal is to kill enemy droids and survive as long as possible. This game was made in 2018 as a school project between Farzad Hayatbakhsh and Toby Tinker. My role was programming and level design. Toby&amp;rsquo;s role was modelling and textures. This game was made using Unity3D, C# and Blender.
Download for Windows</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
